<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>article on silicon punch - tech blog</title>
    <link>https://siliconpunch.com/tags/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in article on silicon punch - tech blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://siliconpunch.com/tags/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/ai/how_to_script_ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/ai/how_to_script_ai/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript API for Adobe illustrator cc22 Ai can be customized and improved at various levels. A first user-friendly level of automation is called ACTIONS. To sum up it is basically recording what the mouse can do with some hickups. Beware though: some functions are not reachable or glitched. To extend the automation scope of the tool, one can use Adobe API called ExtendScript. Things starts to become interesting as Ai would now react as a Command Line Instrustion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/be/be_tools/introduction_to_plm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/be/be_tools/introduction_to_plm/</guid>
      <description>What is called &amp;ldquo;PLM&amp;rdquo; exactly? PLM can be referred as tools used in engineering. This term is not widely known, except from commercials whose goal is to sell tools. Indeed, due to the complexity of engineering topics, tools are more and more connected. This starts from compatibility reasons up to complete cloud solution.
The components of a PLM tool Basically you can get 2 main PLM suites: PTC one and Dassault one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/be/catia0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/be/catia0/</guid>
      <description>catia heads up plop first post
What about Catia? Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/be/redhat0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/be/redhat0/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat Enterprise What is Red Hat? Grosso merdo this is a Linux like, but may have some specific config because it is intended for a very wide usage into a company. You might expect other plugin added above. plop first post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/be/sgd0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/be/sgd0/</guid>
      <description>SGD Sgd is a virtual desktop, or some Jave SE code rendering display locally from a remote desktop. Depending of the version it is highly deprecated.
Fortunately there are amazing compatibilty tweaks.
plop first post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/be/vmw_horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/be/vmw_horizon/</guid>
      <description>Horizon Is a remote client display but it is extremely locked from a client side perspective. As such any unplanified issue may leave you without solution.
Keyboard issue/ Display issue
plop first post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/dev/c_gdb_-_how_to_debug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/dev/c_gdb_-_how_to_debug/</guid>
      <description>how to debug c programs Once a C file is compiled it can be debugged. To do so will requires to improve compilatation by using gcc -g3 file.c then we start our program with adding a gdb prefix. gdb ./a.out tui e b main run [parameters] target record-full s rs q</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>premier article</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/dev/c_programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/dev/c_programs/</guid>
      <description>build c programs A C program is a main function in a file dot c that must be compiled. We will use Gcc by simply executing the command gcc file.c Then we have a new file called binary, that is written for the computer exclusively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>