<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sys-ads on silicon punch - tech blog</title>
    <link>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sys-ads on silicon punch - tech blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>bash config file for terminal use - CLI</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/bashrc-example_with_colored_prompt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/bashrc-example_with_colored_prompt/</guid>
      <description>Bash prompt can be colored This is a modified .bashrc file including fancy colors.
# ~/.bashrc: executed by bash(1) for non-login shells. # see /usr/share/doc/bash/examples/startup-files (in the package bash-doc) # for examples # If not running interactively, don&#39;t do anything [ -z &amp;quot;$PS1&amp;quot; ] &amp;amp;&amp;amp; return # don&#39;t put duplicate lines in the history. See bash(1) for more options # ... or force ignoredups and ignorespace HISTCONTROL=ignoredups:ignorespace # append to the history file, don&#39;t overwrite it shopt -s histappend # for setting history length see HISTSIZE and HISTFILESIZE in bash(1) HISTSIZE=1000 HISTFILESIZE=2000 # check the window size after each command and, if necessary, # update the values of LINES and COLUMNS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bin/bash shell - change shell</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/set_specific-bash-shell_for_user/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/set_specific-bash-shell_for_user/</guid>
      <description>Linux bash shell If user account is set to use sh instead of bash some usual commands may not work. * Does up arrow showing the last command? * Does left arrow allow to move cursor? * Does TAB autocompletes commands? One of these points might showcase an incorrect user profile for shell. To fix it chsh -s /bin/bash  The rootcause can be a badly initialised default config for user accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH using root@machine</title>
      <link>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/best-practise_root_ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:58:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siliconpunch.com/sys-ad/best-practise_root_ssh/</guid>
      <description>Disable root login on SSH To take control on a distant computer on Linux, many system offers a default login by root admin user. Technically you need to know user name and user account password to connect. Therefore anyone willing to connect would just have to guess a password.
what if root access is removed without creating other users? Then server access is lost and would require an intervention to reinstall the system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>